<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AccessiBuddy</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/</link><description>Recent content on AccessiBuddy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 04:43:25 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Formal Usability Study</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/finalref/usabilitystudy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 04:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/finalref/usabilitystudy/</guid><description>What? As part of our process, we conducted a usability study to determine how our interface could be best. In the study, we held most aspects of the interface constant while changing one specific part. Then, we had users try out the different interfaces and collect data on the differences in user behavior between the two.
Motivation After our heuristic evaluation, we decided to put a large emphasis on the flow of our app and the ease of navigation between different frames in our interface.</description></item><item><title>Final Refinement Phase Submission</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/finalref/finalrefinement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 04:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/finalref/finalrefinement/</guid><description>Modifying Design &amp;amp; Implementing Changes In the design refinement stage, our modification process was driven by an overarching goal for our interface that we came up with as a team. We wanted our interface to be very smooth and efficient for the user to navigate through. With this in mind, we started modifying our interface by taking the feedback we got from our heuristic evaluation and making all necessary changes that hindered the usability of our interface.</description></item><item><title>Final Presentation and Figma Prototype</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/finalref/presentation-prototype/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 04:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/finalref/presentation-prototype/</guid><description>Final Presentation At the end of the course, we delivered a presentation on our insights, which is embedded below. Our Figma prototype is also embedded below.
Final Prototype Our final interactive Figma prototype is embedded below.</description></item><item><title>Heuristic Evaluation</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/designref/heuristiceval/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/designref/heuristiceval/</guid><description>As part of our process, another UXD team performed a heuristic evaluation of our user interface prototype we created in Figma. We provided brief instructions to help frame their evaluation. These instructions are below followed by their evaluation.
Figma Prototype Instructions Here is a link to our Figma prototype. It is also embedded below.
User Group You are a person with a mobility restriction looking for something to do around Boston.</description></item><item><title>Design Refinement Phase Submission</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/designref/designrefinement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 14:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/designref/designrefinement/</guid><description>What is your design? How does it work? Our design seeks to make it easier for travelers with physical disabilities to learn about the accessibility of places they want to visit. Although this has slowly been improving in the past years, many existing establishments remain inaccessible to people with certain disabilities. Currently, the primary way people with mobility restrictions figure out if their needs will be met is by calling places.</description></item><item><title>Consent Narrative</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/needsanalysis/consentnarrative/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 14:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/needsanalysis/consentnarrative/</guid><description>Below is an email template for potential interviewees so we can ensure informed consent.
We are a team of five undergraduate students from Olin College of Engineering. We are currently taking a class called User Experience Design, which focuses on designing interfaces that center usability for groups we are not a part of. Our team is designing an app for people with mobility restrictions and we need to learn more about potential users.</description></item><item><title>Design Development Phase Submission</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/designdev/designdevelopment/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 14:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/designdev/designdevelopment/</guid><description>What we&amp;rsquo;ve been working on Our design seeks to make it easier for travelers with physical disabilities to learn about the accessibility of places they want to visit. While the Americans with Disabilities Act seeks to ensure new buildings and spaces are accessible, many existing establishments remain horribly inaccessible to people with certain disabilities. Currently, the primary way people with mobility restrictions figure out if their needs will be met is by calling places.</description></item><item><title>Inspirational Designs</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/needsanalysis/inspirationaldesigns/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 14:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/needsanalysis/inspirationaldesigns/</guid><description>Google Maps - Full team Google Maps view
Good for browsing — “What to see”, “highlights”, etc at top, as well as the “local favorites” Local favorites is a filter to see what the people who live there really like, ensuring you are not falling in any “tourist traps” or similar Map and thumbnail/list view side-by-side, good for filtering and seeing locations of things in list Probably wouldn’t work (as a side-by-side scenario) on a phone — would need separate pages like Airbnb Hotels and stuff accessible from that same home page Bookmarking/saving for later Also good for browsing irl App - Anna irl details view</description></item><item><title>Needs Analysis Phase Submission</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/needsanalysis/needsanalysis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 14:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/needsanalysis/needsanalysis/</guid><description>What problem are you proposing to solve? The problem we are investigating is the difficulty in finding places that are accessible for people with mobility restrictions. This is especially challenging when in a new area and when things like elevators and automatic doors break. Our project will provide current, accurate accessibility information about locations with accessible facilities as well as where certain features may temporarily be broken. The image below is an interaction map of our design.</description></item><item><title>Portfolio</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/portfolio/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 14:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/portfolio/</guid><description>Portfolio of Sketches Interaction Maps Our first interaction map.
Our updated interaction map.</description></item><item><title>Project Brief</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/projectbrief/projectbrief/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 14:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/projectbrief/projectbrief/</guid><description>What is the problem in brief? The problem we are investigating is the difficulty in finding places that are accessible for people with mobility restrictions. This is especially challenging when in a new area and when things like elevators and automatic doors break.
How will your project change the status quo? For whom? Status quo: Google, Yelp, TikTok
Google gives you too many options and doesn’t filter out anything TikTok is engaging, but hard to search for something specific Yelp is annoying and the reviews aren’t always helpful Our project will filter out less desirable options, and help the user decide between what is left.</description></item></channel></rss>