<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Needs Analysis on AccessiBuddy</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/needsanalysis/</link><description>Recent content in Needs Analysis on AccessiBuddy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 14:43:25 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/needsanalysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Consent Narrative</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/needsanalysis/consentnarrative/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 14:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/needsanalysis/consentnarrative/</guid><description>Below is an email template for potential interviewees so we can ensure informed consent.
We are a team of five undergraduate students from Olin College of Engineering. We are currently taking a class called User Experience Design, which focuses on designing interfaces that center usability for groups we are not a part of. Our team is designing an app for people with mobility restrictions and we need to learn more about potential users.</description></item><item><title>Inspirational Designs</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/needsanalysis/inspirationaldesigns/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 14:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/needsanalysis/inspirationaldesigns/</guid><description>Google Maps - Full team Google Maps view
Good for browsing — “What to see”, “highlights”, etc at top, as well as the “local favorites” Local favorites is a filter to see what the people who live there really like, ensuring you are not falling in any “tourist traps” or similar Map and thumbnail/list view side-by-side, good for filtering and seeing locations of things in list Probably wouldn’t work (as a side-by-side scenario) on a phone — would need separate pages like Airbnb Hotels and stuff accessible from that same home page Bookmarking/saving for later Also good for browsing irl App - Anna irl details view</description></item><item><title>Needs Analysis Phase Submission</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/needsanalysis/needsanalysis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 14:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/needsanalysis/needsanalysis/</guid><description>What problem are you proposing to solve? The problem we are investigating is the difficulty in finding places that are accessible for people with mobility restrictions. This is especially challenging when in a new area and when things like elevators and automatic doors break. Our project will provide current, accurate accessibility information about locations with accessible facilities as well as where certain features may temporarily be broken. The image below is an interaction map of our design.</description></item></channel></rss>