<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Febreze</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Febreze</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 14:43:25 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Design Refinement</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/designrefinement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 14:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/designrefinement/</guid><description>What is your design? How does it work? Our design seeks to make it easier for travelers with physical disabilities to learn about the accessibility of places they want to visit. Although this has slowly been improving in the past years, many existing establishments remain inaccessible to people with certain disabilities. Currently, the primary way people with mobility restrictions figure out if their needs will be met is by calling places.</description></item><item><title>Heuristic Evaluation</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/heuristiceval/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 14:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/heuristiceval/</guid><description>As part of our process, another UXD team performed a heuristic evaluation of our user interface prototype we created in Figma. We provided brief instructions to help frame their evaluation. These instructions are below followed by their evaluation.
Figma Prototype Instructions Figma Link
User Group: You are a person with a mobility restriction looking for something to do around Boston. In the case of our prototype, you are looking for somewhere to eat that is accessible to you.</description></item><item><title>Design Development</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/designdevelopment/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 14:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/designdevelopment/</guid><description>What we&amp;rsquo;ve been working on. Our design seeks to make it easier for travelers with physical disabilities to learn about the accessibility of places they want to visit. While the Americans with Disabilities Act seeks to ensure new buildings and spaces are accessible, many existing establishments remain horribly inaccessible to people with certain disabilities. Currently, the primary way people with mobility restrictions figure out if their needs will be met is by calling places.</description></item><item><title>Portfolio</title><link>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/portfolio/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 14:43:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://olincollege.github.io/uxd-2022-03/febreze/portfolio/</guid><description>Portfolio of Sketches Interaction Maps Our first interaction map.
Our updated interaction map.</description></item></channel></rss>